# **KEVIN LEE COX**

210-367-2502 kevincox1983@gmail.com

7334 Crownpiece St. San Antonio, TX 78240

Linkedin.com/in/kevinlee-cox

#### **Profile**

Maintenance Engineer with 14+ years of experience of retail management. Aiming to leverage my proven management and collaboration skills set to begin applying Full-Stack knowledge in order to build interactive/user centered website designs to scale.

## **Work Experience**

Rooms To Go, San Antonio, TX 2007 - Present Porter 2007 - 2008

 Strive to maintain a safe working environment through the prevention of accidents, the preservation of equipment, and the achievement of safe working practices. Trained 2 janitors successfully in all aspects of cleaning, maintenance, and safety procedures, ensuring that they follow pre-set processes for maximum efficiency and achieve high standards

#### Outside Service Technician 2008 - 2015

- Represent the company and travel to customer's homes through daily scheduled routes in San Antonio and surrounding areas.
- Problem solver for customers by utilizing in-depth training provided to decide on the most efficient and best overall solution for each customer's needs, including either repairing furniture (upholstery, wood, etc.) or assisting with replacement products, as needed.

### Retail Facilities Maintenance Engineer 2015 - Present

- Provide technical support and coordination for facility maintenance related items. Coordinates all building and site maintenance. Communicate directly with operations to coordinate facility maintenance repairs. Uses a computerized maintenance management system for tracking work orders, spare parts, and facility equipment maintenance history.
- Manages capital projects, new equipment and construction. Solicit quotes from contractors. Build project budget, timeline, justification and Capital Appropriation Request

# **Education**

Oliver Wendell Holmes High School, Automotive Program, Graduate - 2001

University of Texas at San Antonio, Coding Full Stack Web Development Program, 2020

#### **Skills**

Strong work ethic, adaptability, collaboration, problem solving, divergent thinking, integrity, patience.

#### References

Michael Balderaz, Regional Maintenance Supervisor, Room To Go, mbalderaz@roomstogo.com

Rich Roy, General Manager, Rooms To Go, 210-526-8342